cunard.com 2001-06-18

# Cunard Line

| 

The following information explains our policy regarding any personal information you may supply to us when visiting Cunard.com. 

You can generally visit our web site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information, including your e-mail address. Cunard Line does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis, such as when requesting a brochure or accessing our cruise booking applications. Cunard Line will not share e-mail addresses nor any information submitted by a user when accessing our web site with anyone outside Cunard Line nor will Cunard Line disclose user information to any third party. Our web servers do automatically recognize your domain name when you visit our site, and this information is aggregated and used to measure statistics regarding the use of our site, such as the number of visitors, average time spent on the site, pages viewed and similar information. This information is likewise not distributed to or shared with third parties. 

Cunard Line may use the information it gathers for its own internal purposes. Cunard's goal in collecting personal information online is to continually improve the content of our web site and to offer consumers with cruise products that best meet your preferences and desires. Cunard Line may use the personal data you provide online to send you information about new products and services, or offers that we feel may be of interest to you. However, we will protect your online information in the same manner that we protect our passenger information obtained through other means. 

Cunard Line reserves the right to change this policy at any time. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. By using the Cunard.com site, you signify your agreement with the terms of our privacy statement. If you have any questions about Cunard's privacy policy, please contact us.  

|
